<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Kinematics Calculator</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="toolbar_help">Help</string>

    <string name="activity_name_dh">Notation D-H</string>
    <string name="activity_draw_manipulator">Draw manipulator</string>
    <string name="activity_const_variable">Constants and variables</string>
    <string name="activity_result">Result</string>

    <string name="name_kinematics_forward">Forward Kinematics </string>
    <string name="name_kinematics_inverse">Inverse Kinematics</string>
    <string name="name_change_language">Change Language</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>

    <string name="list_header_lp">i</string>
    <string name="list_header_alpha">α</string>
    <string name="list_header_a">a</string>
    <string name="list_header_theta">Θ</string>
    <string name="list_header_d">d</string>

    <string name="toogle_button_off">C</string>
    <string name="toogle_button_on">V</string>

    <string name="cartesian_manipulator">Cartesian manipulator</string>
    <string name="anthropomorphic_manipulator">Anthropomorphic manipulator</string>
    <string name="cylindrical_manipulator">Cylindrical manipulator</string>
    <string name="spherical_manipulator">Spherical manipulator</string>
    <string name="scara_manipulator">SCARA manipulator</string>

    <string name="add_join">Add Join</string>
    <string name="add_effector">Add Effector</string>
    <string name="undo">Undo</string>
    <string name="nav_header_basic_kinematics_structure">Basic Kinematics Structure</string>

    <string name="help_menu">
        \t The calculator is used to count the tasks forward and inverse kinematics for manipulators with serial kinematic structure. \n
        \t If you want to calculate a forward task kinematics press the "Forward Kinematics" from the main menu \n
        \t If you want to calculate a inverse task kinematics press the "Inverse Kinematics" from the main menu \n
        \t In the application to write the join is used Denavit-Hartenberg notation. According to her are accepted coordinates systems and kinematic parameters.
         There are several steps to be saved data using this notation: \n

        • The Zi axes are drawn along the axis of rotation or the direction of advance; \n
        • The Z-axis gripper are drawn parallel to the Z axis which precedes it; \n
        • Place the center of the local coordinate system Oi, where the common normal axis Zi-1 and Z-axis intersects Zi \n
        • Take Xi axes in such a way that they are common normal axis Z-1 and Z; \n
        • The distance ai is measured along the axis X from the center of the local coordinate system Oi to the intersection of the axes X and Zi-1; \n
        • The distance di is measured along the axis Z from the center of the local coordinate system Oi-1 to the intersection of the axes X and Zi-1; \n
        • The angle of αi is measured between the axes Zi-1 and Zi axis Xi \n
        • The angle θi is measured between the axes Xi-1 and X axis Zi-1. \n

        With so declared manipulator can easily enter the appropriate values to the table displayed in the application. \n

    </string>
</resources>
